Lian Ye.
I'm fine.
Mingyuan!
What happened?
He's been shot.
Over here.
Thank goodness.
The bullet is three centimeters from his heart.
He almost didn't make it.
Quick, gauze!
This is just to keep him alive.
To treat him properly,
we still need antibiotics and painkillers.
Lian Ye, hang in there!
We'll find a way.
We got some intel.
Tomorrow, the Japanese will move supplies
from Fuma Highway to downtown Rongcheng.
Besides medicine for the wounded,
there will be ammo and rations.
We plan to take a team to hijack it.
Along that route,
my officers and I intercepted contraband.
I'll go.
No way. Since they're military supplies,
the Japanese will guard them heavily.
It's too dangerous. Absolutely not.
Captain Xu,
I can give everything I have to fund you,
but he's the only son in our Li family.
He can't be put in danger.
That's where I draw the line.
Dad,
Captain Xu needs to protect the shelter.
It's a huge responsibility.
He can't just leave.
Lian Ye is wounded,
hanging by a thread.
If I don't go now,
do I even deserve to be their comrade?
But...
But this...
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
Did you make contact?
The radio's transmitter is broken.
It can receive messages from Command,
but it can't send any out.
What should we do now?
Get in.
Major General, the Chinese hijacked our military supplies.
I failed in my duty.
Where are those Chinese hiding?
Th-They're like ghosts,
hiding in the mountains.
Send my orders: dispatch reinforcements.
Find them, no matter what.
Yes, Major General.
Why is he burning up?
Could his wound be infected?
If we don't get antibiotics soon,
I'm afraid he won't last much longer.
Got them!
The antibiotics and painkillers you wanted.
Great! He's saved!
We're all going to make it!
Command
hasn't heard from us in a while.
They sent instructions over the radio,
asking us to deliver intel on Rongcheng's
Japanese troop deployments
to Ximen Street.
They'll send someone to receive it,
so we can coordinate from the inside out
to encircle and eliminate Japanese forces,
and liberate the people of Rongcheng.
This is what the guerrillas scouted out—
the intel on Japanese troop deployments.
I called everyone together
mainly to discuss
how to deliver this intel to Ximen Street.
From the mountains to Ximen Street,
the route passes through main streets,
which are full of Japanese checkpoints.
Besides, we just hijacked
Japanese military supplies.
Every Chinese will be strictly searched.
A Chinese person can't pass,
but a Japanese person can.
If I pose as a Japanese officer's family,
claiming to visit the western suburbs,
no one will stop us.
That's a good plan.
It's too dangerous for her to go alone.
I'll go with her.
No way.
You just hijacked the Japanese supplies.
They're looking everywhere for you.
You're too conspicuous. It's a bad idea.
Let me take Dieyi.
I used to pull a rickshaw.
I should take her to Ximen Street.
But...
you're the only son left in your family.
Dieyi is an only child, too.
Mingyuan is his family's only son, too.
My situation is no different.
If anything happens to me,
please take care of my mother.
All right.
It's settled then.
Chen Min and Dali take the intel tomorrow.
They'll send someone to make contact.
Don't forget the secret signal.
Understood.
Don't move.
Your wound will tear open.
I'm fine.
I just want to sit up.
Careful.
Dieyi.
You can't go.
Wait until my wound heals...
I can do it.
So many people die in Rongcheng every day.
The people can't wait another day.
In the entire refugee camp, besides you,
my Japanese is the best.
I can fool them.
No.
It's too dangerous.
Dali is coming with me.
He'll protect me.
Dali is still just a kid.
Don't worry.
I'll come back.
How does it look?
It fits well. It could pass for real.
I'm ready too.
Let's head out.
Dali...
Dali.
I made your favorite oyster omelet.
Take it for the road.
Come back soon.
I'm off, Mom.
Stay safe.
Halt! Routine inspection.
Anna Tanaka.
You are Colonel Tanaka's daughter.
You know my father?
Colonel Tanaka is our commander.
Greetings, Miss Tanaka.
Hello.
Miss Tanaka,
why aren't you traveling by private car?
Chinese rickshaws are quite interesting.
Enjoy your outing, Miss Tanaka.
Let them through.
You, get over here!
Halt!
She's posing as Japanese!
She's an enemy agent!
Bastard!
She's only disguised as Tanaka!
Stop! Get out!
Leave me! Carry on with the mission!
Don't let her get away!
Stop right there!
Over there.